caregiverlist.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy - CaregiverList.com

Caregiverlist, Inc. ("Caregiverlist") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect about you and about your use of the caregiverlist.com site (the "Site"). It will explain the choices you have about how your personal information is used and how we protect that information. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**Information We Collect**

We may collect personal information about you (such as your name, postal address, telephone number and email address) that you provide voluntarily. We use your personal information that you provide to respond to your questions, provide you the specific services you select and send you emails about Site maintenance and updates. 

Even if you do not provide us with personal information, we collect non-personal information about your use of our Site. 

We may use "Cookies" and "Web Beacons" to collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information about your use of our Site. For example, we may use cookies to help you navigate our Site more efficiently and statistically monitor how many people are using our Site. "Cookies" are small text records used by our system that allow us to track user requests and tailor the resulting user experience while on our Site. "Web Beacons" are tiny graphic image files, embedded in a web page in GIF, jpeg or HTML format, that provide a presence on the web page and send back to its home server (which can belong to the host site, a network advertiser or some other third party) information from your browser, such as the IP address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located, the type of browser that is accessing the Site and the ID number of any Cookies on your computer previously placed by that server. Web Beacons may also be used to place a Cookie on your computer. 

**Protection of Children's Personal Information**

The Site is a general audience site and is not designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. 

**Use of your Personal Information**

As a general rule Caregiverlist will not disclose any specific personal information that you submit to us about you ("Personal Information") in a manner that connects you with the Personal Information, except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your Personal Information may be disclosed. 

_Business Partners & Sponsors_: Caregiverlist may disclose some or all of your Personal Information to business partners or sponsors, but this use will be specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give Caregiverlist permission to transfer your Personal Information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your e-mail address will be shared. If more Personal Information will be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer. 

_Third Party & Aggregate Data_: From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you opt to receive information from these third parties, Caregiverlist will (with your permission) share your name and e-mail address with such third parties. Under confidentiality agreements, Caregiverlist may match Personal Information with third party data. Also, Caregiverlist may keep track of what portions of the Web site Customers are visiting and other Customer statistics, and aggregate this information to help us create a better experience for users of our Web site. This is all done without knowing your name or other Personal Information in order to describe our viewers and services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

_Service Providers_ : We contract with other companies and individuals to help us provide services. For example, we may host some of our Site on another company's computer, or we may hire a company to answer customer questions, send information about our products and other services. In order to perform their jobs, these other companies may have limited access to some of the information we maintain about you. We require all such companies to comply with the terms of our Privacy Policy, to limit their access to any personal information to the minimum necessary to perform their obligations, and not to use the information they may access for purposes other than fulfilling their responsibilities to us. 

If we transfer a business unit (such as a subsidiary) or an asset (such as a web site) to another company, we will require them to honor the applicable terms of this Privacy Policy. In the event that Caregiverlist, Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, personally identifiable information will be among the transferred assets. 

We may release personal information to third parties: (1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (2) in special cases, such as in response to a physical threat to you or others, to protect property or defend or assert legal rights. In the event that we are legally compelled to disclose your personal information to a third party, we will attempt to notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order. When we share information with third parties, we ask that they agree in writing to abide by our Privacy Policy. 

Other than the cases described above, we will not release personal information about you to a third party without your consent. 

**Security of your Personal Information**

We have implemented technology and security policies, rules and other measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss. We also protect your information by requiring that all our employees and others who have access to or are associated with the processing of your data respect your confidentiality. 

Although Caregiverlist makes every reasonable attempt to secure your information, there is always some risk in transmitting information over the Internet. There is always a risk that thieves could find some way to circumvent our security systems. Although we take appropriate measures to protect your information, we cannot guarantee that the personal information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**

You should be aware that when you are on Caregiverlist's and/or its affiliates' sites you could hyperlink or be directed to other sites that are beyond our control and/or outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement or a caregiverlist.com search result, the "click" may transfer you off the caregiverlist.com site. These other sites may include sites of advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use Caregiverlist's and/or its affiliates' logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to Customers, collect data, or solicit Information. 

Caregiverlist and its affiliates do not control such sites, and, therefore, are not responsible for their contents or the hyperlinks or advertising they choose to place on such sites. Caregiverlist's and/or its affiliates' inclusion of hyperlinks to these sites do not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites or any association with their operators. Caregiverlist's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, which is beyond Caregiverlist's and its affiliates' control. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out information online (for example, via message boards or chat) that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While Caregiverlist and its affiliates strive to protect their Customers' information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you disclose such information at your own risk. 

**General**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, wish to access your personal information or request that we not use your personal information for a particular purpose, please contact us at **privacy@caregiverlist.com.** We try to answer all inquiries within a reasonable time, but may not always be able to do so. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post changes to the Privacy Policy on our Site only and we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. 

By using this site, you signify your agreement to Caregiverlist's Privacy Policy. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE**. Your continued use of Caregiverlist's and/or its affiliates' sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
